<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
    xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
    xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
    xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/"
    xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
    xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
	<channel>
<title>My RSS Feed</title><link>http://editeodoro.github.io/Bbarolo/index.html</link><description>Hot News&#x21;</description><dc:language>en</dc:language><dc:date>2014-09-09T05:55:29+02:00</dc:date><admin:generatorAgent rdf:resource="http://www.realmacsoftware.com/" />
<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
<sy:updateBase>2000-01-01T12:00+00:00</sy:updateBase>
<lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 06:06:07 +0200</lastBuildDate><item><title>Alice in Wonderland</title><category>Lewis Carroll</category><dc:date>2014-09-09T05:55:29+02:00</dc:date><link>http://editeodoro.github.io/Bbarolo/styled-3/blog/files/7b06f896794b90648cfdc435afe816d2-2.html#unique-entry-id-2</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://editeodoro.github.io/Bbarolo/styled-3/blog/files/7b06f896794b90648cfdc435afe816d2-2.html#unique-entry-id-2</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[<img class="imageStyle" alt="Shower" src="http://editeodoro.github.io/Bbarolo/styled-3/blog/files/shower.jpg" width="2400" height="1590" /><br /><br />&apos;Chorus again!&apos; cried the Gryphon, and the Mock Turtle had just begun  to repeat it, when a cry of &apos;The trial&apos;s beginning!&apos; was heard in the  distance.<br /><br />&apos;Come on!&apos; cried the Gryphon, and, taking Alice by the hand, it hurried  off, without waiting for the end of the song.<br /><br />&apos;What trial is it?&apos; Alice panted as she ran; but the Gryphon only  answered &apos;Come on!&apos; and ran the faster, while more and more faintly  came, carried on the breeze that followed them, the melancholy words:&mdash;<br /><br /><blockquote><p>&apos;Soo&mdash;oop of the e&mdash;e&mdash;evening,       Beautiful, beautiful Soup!&apos;</p></blockquote><br />The King and Queen of Hearts were seated on their throne when they  arrived, with a great crowd assembled about them&mdash;all sorts of little  birds and beasts, as well as the whole pack of cards: the Knave was  standing before them, in chains, with a soldier on each side to guard  him; and near the King was the White Rabbit, with a trumpet in one hand,  and a scroll of parchment in the other. In the very middle of the court  was a table, with a large dish of tarts upon it: they looked so good,  that it made Alice quite hungry to look at them&mdash;&apos;I wish they&apos;d get the  trial done,&apos; she thought, &apos;and hand round the refreshments!&apos; But there  seemed to be no chance of this, so she began looking at everything about  her, to pass away the time.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>The Scarlet Plague</title><category>Jack London</category><dc:date>2014-09-09T05:55:29+02:00</dc:date><link>http://editeodoro.github.io/Bbarolo/styled-3/blog/files/2c59dfc4387dd326cc38c868da1e209e-1.html#unique-entry-id-1</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://editeodoro.github.io/Bbarolo/styled-3/blog/files/2c59dfc4387dd326cc38c868da1e209e-1.html#unique-entry-id-1</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA["The heart began to beat faster and the heat of the body to increase. Then came the scarlet rash, spreading like wildfire over the face and body. Most persons never noticed the increase in heat and heart-beat, and the first they knew was when the scarlet rash came out. Usually, they had convulsions at the time of the appearance of the rash. But these convulsions did not last long and were not very severe. If one lived through them, he became perfectly quiet, and only did he feel a numbness swiftly creeping up his body from the feet. The heels became numb first, then the legs, and hips, and when the numbness reached as high as his heart he died. They did not rave or sleep. Their minds always remained cool and calm up to the moment their heart numbed and stopped. And another strange thing was the rapidity of decomposition. No sooner was a person dead than the body seemed to fall to pieces, to fly apart, to melt away even as you looked at it. That was one of the reasons the plague spread so rapidly. All the billions of germs in a corpse were so immediately released.<br /><br />"And it was because of all this that the bacteriologists had so little chance in fighting the germs. They were killed in their laboratories even as they studied the germ of the Scarlet Death. They were heroes. As fast as they perished, others stepped forth and took their places. It was in London that they first isolated it. The news was telegraphed everywhere. Trask was the name of the man who succeeded in this, but within thirty hours he was dead. Then came the struggle in all the laboratories to find something that would kill the plague germs. All drugs failed. You see, the problem was to get a drug, or serum, that would kill the germs in the body and not kill the body. They tried to fight it with other germs, to put into the body of a sick man germs that were the enemies of the plague germs&mdash;"<br /><br />"And it was because of all this that the bacteriologists had so little chance in fighting the germs. They were killed in their laboratories even as they studied the germ of the Scarlet Death. They were heroes. As fast as they perished, others stepped forth and took their places. It was in London that they first isolated it. The news was telegraphed everywhere. Trask was the name of the man who succeeded in this, but within thirty hours he was dead. Then came the struggle in all the laboratories to find something that would kill the plague germs. All drugs failed. You see, the problem was to get a drug, or serum, that would kill the germs in the body and not kill the body. They tried to fight it with other germs, to put into the body of a sick man germs that were the enemies of the plague germs&mdash;"<br /><br />"And you can&apos;t see these germ-things, Granser," Hare-Lip objected, "and here you gabble, gabble, gabble about them as if they was anything, when they&apos;re nothing at all. Anything you can&apos;t see, ain&apos;t, that&apos;s what. Fighting things that ain&apos;t with things that ain&apos;t! They must have been all fools in them days. That&apos;s why they croaked. I ain&apos;t goin&apos; to believe in such rot, I tell you that."<br /><br />Granser promptly began to weep, while Edwin hotly took up his defence.]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>A Princess of Mars</title><dc:subject>Blog</dc:subject><dc:date>2014-09-09T05:55:29+02:00</dc:date><link>http://editeodoro.github.io/Bbarolo/styled-3/blog/files/d209e09813d9da21deaca114a509e45f-0.html#unique-entry-id-0</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://editeodoro.github.io/Bbarolo/styled-3/blog/files/d209e09813d9da21deaca114a509e45f-0.html#unique-entry-id-0</guid><content:encoded><![CDATA[The women and children of a man&apos;s retinue may be likened to a military unit for which he is responsible in various ways, as in matters of instruction, discipline, sustenance, and the exigencies of their continual roamings and their unending strife with other communities and with the red Martians. His women are in no sense wives. The green Martians use no word corresponding in meaning with this earthly word. <br /><br />Their mating is a matter of community interest solely, and is directed without reference to natural selection. The council of chieftains of each community control the matter as surely as the owner of a Kentucky racing stud directs the scientific breeding of his stock for the improvement of the whole.<br /><br />In theory it may sound well, as is often the case with theories, but the results of ages of this unnatural practice, coupled with the community interest in the offspring being held paramount to that of the mother, is shown in the cold, cruel creatures, and their gloomy, loveless, mirthless existence.<br /><br />It is true that the green Martians are absolutely virtuous, both men and women, with the exception of such degenerates as Tal Hajus; but better far a finer balance of human characteristics even at the expense of a slight and occasional loss of chastity.<br /><br />Finding that I must assume responsibility for these creatures, whether I would or not, I made the best of it and directed them to find quarters on the upper floors, leaving the third floor to me. One of the girls I charged with the duties of my simple cuisine, and directed the others to take up the various activities which had formerly constituted their vocations. Thereafter I saw little of them, nor did I care to.<br /><br />Following the battle with the air ships, the community remained within the city for several days, abandoning the homeward march until they could feel reasonably assured that the ships would not return; for to be caught on the open plains with a cavalcade of chariots and children was far from the desire of even so warlike a people as the green Martians.]]></content:encoded></item></channel>
</rss>